[
    {
        "question": "Which country is Thimphu its capital?",
        "answer": "Bhutan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Ouagadougou its capital?",
        "answer": "Burkina Faso"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Mbabane its capital?",
        "answer": "Eswatini"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Paramaribo its capital?",
        "answer": "Suriname"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Ngerulmud its capital?",
        "answer": "Palau"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Lilongwe its capital?",
        "answer": "Malawi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Nuku'alofa its capital?",
        "answer": "Tonga"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Tarawa its capital?",
        "answer": "Kiribati"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Maseru its capital?",
        "answer": "Lesotho"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Moroni its capital?",
        "answer": "Comoros"
    }
]